

CONTACT ME

+971 56445 1682

sharjah,UAE

abhiramps776@gmail.com

https://abhiramps.vercel.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ abhiram-p-s-947b92157/

https://github.com/abhiramps

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• ReactJS,NextJs

●●●● Tailwindcss,chakraUI

●●●● Bootstrap5,materialUI

•••• HTML5,CSS3,SCSS

●●● AWS amplify,Cognito,S3 bucket

●●●● AWS IoT,Lambda,AppSync

•••• REST,GraphQl API

•••• Prisma ORM

GIT,Github

•••• Responsive,UI/UX

Redux.ExpressJs

●●●● DynamoDb,MongoDB,PlanetScale

●●●● Vercel,Heroku,Netlify



ABHIRAM PS

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

As a Fullstack stack developer, I have nearly a year of experience and knowledge of web development technologies, including, NextJs, Aws Amplify, Github, and DynamoDb.

I seek the opportunity to prove my skills in a demanding environment and to utilize my knowledge and intelligence in order to enhance the success of the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Shaikhtech, UAE | Dec 2021 - April 2022

- Designed and Developed a Real-time NextJS Web application that interacts with IoT devices through AWS cloud via AWS IOT MQTT connection using AWS Amplify framework and Appsync.Created Amplify Graphql API for querying History data from DynamoDb. Implemented user management with AWS Cognito and Lambda function.
- Developed an Enterprise application for managing and displaying the assets of real estate brokers by integrating with the Matterport platform.

JUNIOR MERN STACK DEVELOPER

Enfin technologies, INDIA | Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

- Assisted the development of web applications.
- Report daily status to senior developers.
- Builds and shapes a visitor's experience on the site.
- Creates page layouts, site style, and page features

AWARDS RECEIVED

- NACTET Certification MEA(R)N STACK
 DEVELOPMENT (Nov 2020 Apr 2021)
- Web development ICT Academy
 (July 2017 5 days)

PERSONAL DETAILS

AGE : 24 years

NATIONALITY : Indian

MARITAL STATUS : Single

VISA STATUS : Visit Visa valid

till june 20

LANGUAGES

English (Professional working proficiency)

Malayalam (Native)

REFERENCE

Mr. V.Sunil Kumar

Director of Engineering sunil@shaikh-tech.com

+971 50 216 5580

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER TRAINEE

Luminar technolab, INDIA | 2020 nov -2021 april

- Created Web applications using ReactJs, Angular11 and backend with ExpressJs.Collaborated with other designers
- Report daily status to senior developers.

PROJECTS

FLEET MANAGEMENT

Client: WORLD STAR | Dec 2021 - Present

- A Fuel delivery system for managing and processing Real-time data of customers via AWS IOT MQTT protocol and displaying it on the front end.
- Built using AWS amplify for managing backend environment, Amplify Graphql for API, Amazon Cognito User Pools for managing authentication.
- Technologies used: NextJs, ChakraUI, AWS Amplify, Graphql, cogito,react-hook-from,DynamoDb

Demonstration Link:

https://test.dx3l5bsdsih29.amplifyapp.com/

ALEFVR

Client:Sedra Roshn | Jan 2022 - Present

- Alef is a digital property asset management platform that serves as the central platform for managing and viewing all property 3D models – both digital twins of existing physical assets as well as virtually created assets.
- Integrated SDK provided by Matterport for displaying the 3D scanned assets used by Matterport camera.
- **Technologies used**: NextJs,ChakraUI,Typescript, apollo graphql,Nexus,PrismaORM,Planetscale,NextAuth

Demonstration Link: https://www.alefvr.com/

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

APJ ABDUL KALAM TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY, INDIA

BE/B.TECH in Computer science and Engineering | Aug 2016 - Oct 2020